chekrs.com 2019-01-30

# Privacy policy chekrs.com, jobs, schools, entrance

## **Chekrs Privacy Policy**

  * The privacy policy entitled by Chekrs adheres to all the products and services offered at chekrs.com and sites linked to chekrs.com (the **Chekrs Platform** run by Crazzle Plus InfoTech having its registered office at A (1) PLOT NO-11, NANU MARG, DEVI NAGAR, NEW SANGANER ROAD, GURJAR KI THADI, JAIPUR). The policies govern the manner in which Chekrs collects, maintains the record, uses and discloses it from the users/visitors.

 **Personal Information Policy:**

We are committed to respect your personal information that you share with us and recognize your urge for its protection. For every user visiting the website or our team may collect to collect their information in variety of ways and not limited. When a user visits, register, take subscription, fill out forms or accesses services asking appropriate details like name, email address, phone number and the mailing address. The users can visit the site anonymously however to access a few of the premium services you can be asked to share valid details.

To fulfill the purpose we will be collecting information only if you provide them voluntarily to us. Being a user you can always refuse to share your identification and details, except that it would restrain you from engaging in proceeding of related activities.

 **Non-personal identification Policy:**

Whenever a user visits or interacts our website we may collect their non personal information. Under the non personal information technical information is accessed by us. It may include browser name, details of the computer, its type, and connection, operating systems, ISP (Internet Service Provider) and other similar information. We may also collect the non personal information to analyze the statics and trends.

 **Cookies:**

To enhance the user experience our site may use “cookies”. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used to collect the activities related to the website. These cookies can be placed by the user’s browsers on their hard drive. These cookies can sometimes be used for record keeping or sometimes to track information about them. Your browser may ask you to remove cookie however them you will be required to enter your details manually while some parts may not function properly.

 **How we use the information:**

The information that is share with Chekrs (same applies for Crazzle Plus InfoTech from whom the **Chekrs Platform** is being run) can be used for the following purposes-

  * To improve customer service: The information that you provides us helps us track the record, respond in line and provide enhanced support requirements.
  * To customize user experience: We may use your information and activity to understand how the services and resources can be provided to the users to stay intact.
  * To improve: Focusing on the result oriented services, you information will be useful as feedback on changes that needs to be done.
  * To promote content, survey, contest or any other site feature.
  * To show the information that the users have agreed/ accepted to receive as per their interest.
  * To periodically send you the emails for informing updates as per your interest.

If you are interested to receive the mails you can unsubscribe them to avoid receiving future emails. The detailed instruction can be followed from the instructions anytime you want to. Further if you are interested to receive more such updates we can be contacted anytime.

 **Protection of your information:**

We adopt appropriate data collection to avoid any kind of leakage. All your vulnerable personal details such as the username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site is accessed with security measures to protect it against any unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or sharing.

The sharing of your private data and the website happens over a secured SSL communication channel which is secured and encrypted with digital enclosures.

We restrict access of your information to the employees who need it to develop, operate and improve services of the website.

 **Sharing of your information:**

We restrain any selling, trading or renting the personal information shared by our users to others. However some of the generic demographic information which is not linked to any personal identification of any user/visitor is shared with our business partners, advertisers, trusted affiliates for outlined purposes.

We may seek third parties to provide you the newsletters or surveys to help regulate our business. For this limited purpose we may share your information with these third parties when you have granted permission. However these parties will not have any individual rights to share your information.

 **Third Party Websites:**

Users may find advertisements on the site that links to the services of our advertisers, sponsors, licensors, suppliers, partners and other third parties as per business. We do not control the links or content that appears on these websites and advertisements to or from our sites. Also, we do not control the practices employed by these websites. These websites may have their own terms and conditions and customer policies.

We are not liable for sharing the personal information asked in any way to these third parties (ads displayed on the website while viewing the services of Chekrs)

 **Advertising:**

The ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertisers who may also set cookies. These cookies will allow the third parties to recognize your computer details each time and show you or others who use your computer the online advertisement. This information will allow the ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they have seen from your activity and believe will interest you.

Some of the ads while website are also served by the Google Adsense.  Google often uses the DART (Dynamic Advertising Reporting & Targeting) Cookie which helps it to show the ads based on user’s visit and activities on our site and other websites on Internet. However this uses the non personal identifiable information and not any personal information.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

Chekrs reserves the right to update, change or modify this policy at any time as per requirement. The policy shall come to effect right after any such update, change or modification.

 **Acceptance to the policies:**

By using this website you accept polices listed here. If objectionable please do not use our website. Your use to the website with changes in the privacy policies signify your acceptance to those changed polices.

 **Contact Us:**

If you have any concerns or queries regarding the policies, we will employ all reasonable and possible efforts for same. Chekrs welcomes your initiate to reach us at following address.

Email: chekrs@gmail.com
